solarplaza.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Statement | Solarplaza | The global solar energy (PV) platform

**Solarplaza Privacy Policy**

(“Solarplaza B.V.,” “we” or “us”) created this privacy policy to give you confidence as you visit and use the Solarplaza website (the “Site”), and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this privacy policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. It is your responsibility to review this privacy policy from time to time to ensure that you continue to agree with all of its terms. 

**How and Why We Collect and Use Information**

Our servers automatically recognize visitors’ domain names and IP addresses (the number assigned to computers on the Internet). No personal information about you is revealed in this process. The Site may also gather anonymous “traffic data” that does not personally identify you, but that may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the services we offer. We may use anonymous information to analyze Site traffic, but we do not examine this information for individually identifying information. In addition, we may use anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer the Site, or to display the content according to your preferences. 

Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis. 

You do not have to give us any of your personal information to use the Site. If you choose to create a “Solarplaza Profile” on the Site, any information you add to the public portion of a Solarplaza Profile will be available to us as well as to other users of the Site. 

**Children's Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect or save any information from children under the age of 13. 

**Cookies**

We may use cookies to improve your experience using the Site. These cookies do not generally allow us to personally identify a specific user. 

**Disclosure**

We may need to share your information with any of the companies that help provide the Solarplaza service. We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Solarplaza or itss parent company, subsidiaries or affiliates, (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Solarplaza or the users of the Site, or (3) act under exigent circumstances to protect the safety of the public or users of the Site. 

**Public Forums**

The Site may include interactive forums such as message boards and chat rooms. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Sale or Change of Control**

If Solarplaza or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your information will be one of the assets transferred to the acquirer. 

**Links to Third Party Sites**

If you follow any of the links you find on this Site, our privacy policy does not extend to third party sites. 

**Security**

To help protect your personal information we may use security measures, including encryption and password protection. 

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, email us at johan@solarplaza.com
